OURI: Hey, you!
OURI: If I become the center, come over to me!
OURI: Huh?
UTAGE: Are you asking me to be your housekeeper?
OURI: What?!
UTAGE: I can't actually take on any more shifts,
UTAGE: so you'll have to hire someone else...
OURI: Shut up!
OURI: Then stop coming here so much
and open up your schedule!
UTAGE: Why in the world would I do that?
OURI: If you know that Tamon's gonna win,
OURI: you shouldn't have any problem with that.
OURI: Or do you actually
think he's going to lose?
UTAGE: I accept.
TAMON: Huh?
UTAGE: Oh, good morning,
UTAGE: Fukuhara-sama.
TAMON: U-U-U-Um...
OURI: Hmph.
OURI: You're about to find out how big
a mistake it was to talk to me like that.
OURI: You better be prepared.
UTAGE: Crap.
LYRICS: Hey!! It's just like sweeet magic!! Aha!
LYRICS: Hi, it's me!
The one with that killer smile!
LYRICS: Stealing your gaze with a shocking style!
LYRICS: Smooth as ever, I escort you
LYRICS: And this voice, seducing you
LYRICS: Ah, come on, let's dance;
I'm aiming straight for your heart
LYRICS: I am your ace darlin'
LYRICS: Confidence? Yeah, I've got plenty
LYRICS: Please Please
LYRICS: Whisper just to me, call my name
LYRICS: You're too popular,
it drives me crazy and I'm not okay
LYRICS: But I'm sorry, losing's not my thing
LYRICS: Hey, girl
LYRICS: Look this way!
LYRICS: I see your smile, smile, smile,
I wanna make it all mine
LYRICS: Crash, crash, crash,
our special connection shines
LYRICS: Dance, dance,
our world is non-stop groovin'
LYRICS: I'll show you my perfect
A-side, side, side
LYRICS: And my private B-side, side, side;
I'll show you everything
LYRICS: So take my hand and let's roll
LYRICS: Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
LYRICS: Sweetie honey Sweetie honey
LYRICS: It's a spell that makes your heart race
LYRICS: We can't go back
LYRICS: You're falling in love with me, c'mon!
LYRICS: Sweetie honey
LYRICS: Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
UTAGE: I'm sorry I accepted that bet!
SIGN: You're a Sniper of Love
UTAGE: But after he said all that,
UTAGE: I couldn't bring myself to say,
"Tamon-kun can't win, " even as a lie.
UTAGE: Please pay no mind to what just happened
UTAGE: and do your best
at your own pace, Gloomyhara-san.
TAMON: No.
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: You can't leave me...
UTAGE: Well, yes, I probably shouldn't.
UTAGE: Fujita-san asked me
to take care of the housework,
UTAGE: so it's not like I can go elsewhere.
UTAGE: That was thoughtless of me. I'm sorry.
TAMON: No, this is all because
I made it so musty in here.
TAMON: I'll buy a dehumidifier.
UTAGE: If there's anything that I can do
to help you win, please let me know.
UTAGE: You can count on me to
get all the housework done, though!
UTAGE: Here's some barley tea.
TAMON: Thank you very much.
TAMON: I've looked up to idols
ever since I was little.
TAMON: That's all that was on my mind.
UTAGE: Oh, I wuv you.
TAMON: I do love all my fans...
TAMON: but I've never experienced really
falling in love with just one person.
TAMON: What exactly is love?
UTAGE: Huh?
UTAGE: I mean, I do love you
and only you, Tamon-kun,
UTAGE: but it's a different kind of love
from how most would define it.
TAMON: Oh, then...
TAMON: Would you go to a festival with me?
UTAGE: I can't see where this is going.
SIGN: Festival
HOTTIEHARAS: Sexy! Wild! Sexy! Wild! Sexy! Wild!
UTAGE: Me? Go to a festival with Tamon-kun?!
UTAGE: I mean, there's a never-ending
Tamon Fes going on in my brain, but...
TAMON: If I'm going to sing about heartbreak,
I should learn about love first, right?
TAMON: So... that's exactly why I have to go.
SIGN: Love
TAMON: Bursts fly up, then fall.
And once they fall, they fly up again.
SIGN: Romance
TAMON: They say that people gather there
in search for true love.
RANDO GUY: I'm so glad I came here with you.
RANDO GIRL: Me, too.
TAMON: Is what awaits them
a new encounter or goodbyes?
RANDO GUY 2: Wait! You've got it all wrong!
RANDO GIRL 2: You liar! You love her, don't you?!
TAMON: The sanctuary for lovers passed down
since time immemorial.
TAMON: Its name... the summer festival!
SIGN: Summer Festival
UTAGE: Tamon-kun?
TAMON: I want to go there and find out
what love actually is.
TAMON: I want to win the second round
in our competition to decide the center!
TAMON: But...
TAMON: if I went into that kind of
dazzling party night all by myself,
TAMON: the sheer amount of positive energy
might reduce me to cinders...
TAMON: So I just can't build up the courage.
UTAGE: Now, wait. Where in the world did you get
this kind of information about festivals?
TAMON: That's what Love Specialist-san told me.
SIGN: Everyone's Guidance Room
SIGN: Advanced
Search
SIGN: Question Resolved
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Gloomy-san
SIGN: I'm a guy in his 3rd year of high school.
I don't understand what love is. Please tell me.
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: 1 Answer
SIGN: New
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: The Love Specialist-san
SIGN: I, too, had a period in my life like that.
First, you need to do everything you can
to get yourself to a summer festival.
Bursts fly up, then fall. And once they fall,
they fly up again. They say that people
gather there in search for true love.
UTAGE: Love Specialist...
TAMON: Kinoshita-san, will you go with me?
UTAGE: The only way a lone fan would be allowed
to go with Tamon-kun to a summer festival
UTAGE: is in their own delusions!
UTAGE: I know I said that I would do
anything to help, but I'm very sorry.
UTAGE: I decl...
TAMON: Utage.
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: I need this summer festival.
TAMON: You're the only one...
I can ask to do this with me, right?
ANNOUNCER: Our guest today is an actor
who represents Japan
ANNOUNCER: who has spread his work overseas
in the past few years
ANNOUNCER: and is making his mark in the industry...
ANNOUNCER: The actor, Toshikazu Sakaguchi.
SIGN: Toshikazu Sakaguchi
ANNOUNCER: He's known to love his wife,
the singer, SHIORI, very much.
SIGN: Toshikazu Sakaguchi
ANNOUNCER: And this very happy couple
continues to work on the front lines
ANNOUNCER: of their respective fields
in the entertainment industry.
ANNOUNCER: And of course, the one who
everyone is talking about right now
ANNOUNCER: is their son who debuted
as a singer, Ouri Sakaguchi.
SIGN: Toshikazu Sakaguchi
SIGN: Ouri Sakaguchi
ANNOUNCER: A whole family of
huge celebrities!
OURI: The fans, the people
in the entertainment industry,
ANNOUNCER: Sakaguchi-san says
that no matter how busy he is,
ANNOUNCER: he always makes time for his family.
OURI: and even those with no interest in me...
OURI: They'd at least change their tone
a little if they approached me.
ANNOUNCER: In this episode, we'll be looking into
ANNOUNCER: his never-before-seen
time management skills.
OURI: And yet, that woman...
OURI: Hmm?
OURI: He's going out this late?
OURI: Who does he think he is?
FESTIVAL: Seiya! Seiya! Seiya!
LITTLE BOY: Hey, buy me that mask.
MOM: Oh, fine.
UTAGE: If Tamon-kun thinks it's necessary,
UTAGE: I will do everything I can
to help out in his search for love...
UTAGE: As his housekeeper.
RANDO GUY: Oh, man! I guess we're
having a triple date today.
RANDO GIRL: Talk about enjoying our youth!
UTAGE: This is just another form of housework.
TAMON: Kinoshita-san...
TAMON: A yukata—
UTAGE: Black hair!
UTAGE: Is that a wig? It really suits you!
TAMON: Yes. The paper bag makes it hard to see,
and it's even worse at night.
UTAGE: Thank goodness it's Gloomyhara-san.
UTAGE: Hottiehara-kun would've had fireworks
shooting out of my head right now.
OURI: What's that woman doing here?
UTAGE: Okay, let's go.
OURI: Wait, are those two going out?!
TAMON: Right.
UTAGE: Wow...
UTAGE: There's still time before the fireworks.
SIGN: Yakisoba
UTAGE: Why don't we visit some stalls
in the meantime... Huh?
TAMON: Love... Where's love?
TAMON: It's hot... Where's... love?
UTAGE: I won't let anyone report Tamon-kun!
TAMON: It's really hot.
SIGN: Yakisoba | Okonomiyaki | Ice Ice Ice | Goldfish
TAMON: Is this heat being emitted
from all the couples around here?
SIGN: Cotton Candy
UTAGE: Er... It's just the air temperature.
TAMON: Oh... Um...
TAMON: I didn't get to finish my sentence
earlier... But your yukata—
UTAGE: Ah!
UTAGE: Look over there!
SIGN: Shooting Gallery
RANDO GIRL: Hey, this looks impossible.
UTAGE: A guy is trying to show off to a girl!
SIGN: No losers here
Consolation Prize
Yucky Sticks
RANDO GUY: Nah, it's all good.
TAMON: Is that love?!
SIGN: No losers here
Consolation Prize
Yucky Sticks
SIGN:
SIGN: Chocorooms
Mushroom Mountain
SIGN: Apollo
TAMON: Th-That's amazing! Congratulations!
UTAGE: This is nothing compared
to trying to win concert tickets.
UTAGE: Of course, I made sure not to
shoot your face, Tamon-kun.
SIGN: No losers here
Consolation Prize
Yucky Sticks
SIGN: Yucky Stick
Chocolate Shiso/Shiitake Flavor
TAMON: What should I do?
TAMON: If I don't learn
a single thing about love,
TAMON: then I just came here
to get bit by mosquitos!
TAMON: I knew an introvert like me
shouldn't have come to a place like this.
TAMON: It's itchy, it's scary, it's hot!
UTAGE: You've always masterfully shot
through the hearts of the fans.
UTAGE: You're a cupid of love... no.
UTAGE: You're a sniper of love!
TAMON: Bang!
UTAGE: So please don't give up.
UTAGE: I'm sure you'll be able to find out
UTAGE: what love actually means, Tamon-kun!
TAMON: I'll do my best.
OURI: Seriously, what's their
actual relationship?
UTAGE: Oh, look!
UTAGE: There's a couple over there
sharing some takoyaki!
RANDO GIRL: Open up, Ta-kun!
RANDO GUY: Aah!
TAMON: I-Is that love?!
RANDO GUY: Yum.
TAMON: So this is... love.
UTAGE: No, that's takoyaki.
TAMON: I'm going to give it all I've got.
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: Say, "Aah."
TAMON: Come on. Open up.
OURI: Look how close they are!
Wait, are they really?!
TAMON: Kinoshita-san!
OURI: Seriously, which is it?!
TAMON: Come on. Don't get lost.
TAMON: Make sure you hang onto me.
UTAGE: Is...
UTAGE: Is this...
TAMON: Your tongue's all red.
UTAGE: A world where Tamon-kun's
living as a normal person?!
TAMON: Do your feet hurt?
UTAGE: No! There is no "normal person"
like this in existence!
UTAGE: My head's a full-on carnival right now,
UTAGE: so I'm not going to be
able to help find any love!
TAMON: Kinoshita-san!
TAMON: Are you okay, Kinoshita-san?!
UTAGE: I'm so sorry that I'm an otaku.
TAMON: It's okay.
TAMON: The fact that happened must mean I'm just
not understanding this love thing right.
SIGN: Gloooom
TAMON: I'll go buy us something to drink.
UTAGE: Thank you.
UTAGE: Love, huh...
UTAGE: I talked a big game,
but in the end, I'm just an otaku.
UTAGE: I just can't see Tamon-kun
as a normal guy.
OURI: I still have no idea
if they're actually dating or not,
OURI: and it's pissing me off.
OURI: Good evening!
OURI: Here by yourself?
UTAGE: I'm sorry?
SIGN: Ramune
TAMON: I hope that Kinoshita-san likes ramune.
SIGN: Cotton Candy
TAMON: But your yukata—
UTAGE: Ah!
UTAGE: Look over there!
UTAGE: Oh, no. He's not my boyfriend.
UTAGE: He's just an acquaintance.
OURI: I see. S-So you don't have a boyfriend.
UTAGE: Right.
UTAGE: Actually, I don't even
really understand love.
UTAGE: So you're hitting on the wrong person.
UTAGE: There's plenty of other cuties
out there, aren't there?
OURI: What the hell?
OURI: Your yukata looks pretty good on you.
UTAGE: Huh? Um... thank you...
OURI: She almost seems sweet here,
and it's throwing me off.
TAMON: Excuse me.
TAMON: Could you please not talk to her?
TAMON: She's my girlfriend.
UTAGE: Huh?
UTAGE: Huh? What? U-Um, wha—
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san?!
OURI: Seriously?
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san!
UTAGE: I-I know you said that
to stop that guy from hitting on me,
UTAGE: but your face...
UTAGE: If that guy realizes
that you're Tamon-kun...
TAMON: I also...
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: I also thought that, too.
TAMON: You look really lovely in that yukata.
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: I'm sorry I said it so late!
TAMON: It must be horrific to hear that
from someone like me!
TAMON: I'm sorry for exposing you to
paranormal phenomena!
UTAGE: Huh? Um? That made me happy!
Really happy to hear that!
TAMON: But you're clearly weirded out!
UTAGE: It just surprised me because
I'm not used to getting compliments!
UTAGE: At that moment... just for a moment...
UTAGE: I saw Tamon-kun...
UTAGE: as a guy.
UTAGE: We came to this summer festival so he
could try to find out what love really is.
UTAGE: But...
TAMON: I'm so sorry.
TAMON: To copy other people in order
to find out what love is...
TAMON: Thinking about it rationally,
it was just a fool's errand.
TAMON: If I'm just going to spend the rest
of my life mocked by others...
TAMON: I'd like to just end things right now.
Just living is my dark history!
SIGN: Love
UTAGE: Now he's just lost all hope.
TAMON: Love?
TAMON: That's exactly what you're feeling
when you're thinking about me.
UTAGE: Seriously, how does Gloomyhara-san
pull off that persona?
UTAGE: No. Right now, I need to do
whatever I can for Gloomyhara-san.
TAMON: Does love actually exist?
UTAGE: Yes! You said so yourself, Tamon-kun!
TAMON: But I've realized that just trying
to copy others doesn't work.
TAMON: I mean, I don't even usually go places
with someone else like this.
TAMON: I'm kinda jealous...
UTAGE: Let's both stop doing things
we're not used to.
TAMON: Huh?
UTAGE: Not to mention, this is a very rare
day off for you, Gloomyhara-san.
UTAGE: So why don't we just try
to enjoy our time normally?
UTAGE: Not as a client and his housekeeper,
but just as friends.
TAMON: Friends...
UTAGE: I definitely somehow
hit him in the feels right there.
TAMON: I'm sorry—
TAMON: The only ones I've been able to open up
to are basically the stains on my walls,
TAMON: so just hearing the word "friends"
was just too much...
UTAGE: Tamon-kun... What happened to you?
TAMON: Yes, you're right.
TAMON: I think I tried to skip too many steps.
TAMON: I'm sorry that I tried to fly
when I'm only a caterpillar.
UTAGE: Rather than a caterpillar...
UTAGE: I'd say you're more like
a fallen angel that's lost his wings.
UTAGE: Please take that back.
TAMON: I-I'm sorry that I tried to fly
when I'm just a fallen angel.
TAMON: Um...
UTAGE: Yes?
TAMON: May I call you "Master Kinoshita"?
UTAGE: Say what now?
TAMON: Being friends means that
we're closer than two strangers, right?
TAMON: So I thought it'd be important
to pay you the proper respect.
UTAGE: I definitely never thought of that.
UTAGE: I honestly don't know how to handle that.
UTAGE: Being called "Master" by a literal god
is just too confusing.
TAMON: Well, what do people usually call you?
UTAGE: My friends call me "Utage, "
UTAGE: but you're older than me,
so you can just call me "Kinoshita."
TAMON: There's no way I can just call you
by your name like that!
TAMON: Actually, you should just
call me "Garbagehara!"
UTAGE: What are you talking about?!
UTAGE: I'll be calling you Gloomyhara-senpai!
TAMON: Huh?!
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-senpai!
TAMON: Kino...
UTAGE: Anyway, you can call me
whatever you'd like.
TAMON: B-But...
UTAGE: You don't use any honorifics
when you're Hottiehara-kun.
TAMON: That's true...
TAMON: U-Uta...
UTAGE: Ah!
UTAGE: Hurry, Gloomyhara-senpai!
TAMON: R-Right...
UTAGE: Let's dance.
UTAGE: Tamon-kun's always working so hard.
UTAGE: He deserves a moment to enjoy
being a high school student.
SIGN: Yo-Yo Fishing
SIGN: Fried Potatoes
UTAGE: So just for now, we'll be friends.
UTAGE: Just for today.
GUY: Huh?
TAMON: Please don't hate me!
Please don't hate me!
UTAGE: You've got this! Just stay calm!
UTAGE: I wonder if this is what
Gloomyhara-san would be like
UTAGE: as a normal high school student.
SIGN: Ice Pops
UTAGE: Sorry to keep you waiting.
UTAGE: Here you go.
TAMON: Th-Thank you very...
UTAGE: Squee.
TAMON: Sorry, my hands were full,
and I didn't want your yukata to get d...
SIGN: Brain Freeze
TAMON: O-Ow!
UTAGE: No, I'm sorry!
UTAGE: It's almost time for the fireworks.
UTAGE: I know a secret spot,
so let's go over there.
UTAGE: You can probably take your mask off here.
TAMON: Right.
TAMON: It was so hot...
UTAGE: His usual hair color.
I definitely feel more at ease now.
UTAGE: You dyed your hair during
your audition, right?
UTAGE: It caused quite a stir among fans
because of the sudden change.
TAMON: Yes... I decided to go all-out and dye it
TAMON: a color that I thought was
the complete opposite of me.
TAMON: Ever since then, when I stand
before people as an idol, I'm Hottiehara.
UTAGE: Now, everyone loves that pink hair.
UTAGE: When you first appeared with that hair,
UTAGE: all the fans fell in love and
everyone called pink the color of love.
SIGN: #TheSexyKindOfPink
SIGN: #ArrestedForSexyCrimes
SIGN: #IDon'tCareIfIt'sADreamJustTakeMeAlready
SIGN: Pink
SIGN: Color     of     Love
TAMON: Oh, really?
TAMON: We came here searching for it
since I didn't know what it is,
TAMON: so that's a bit ironic to hear.
UTAGE: In reality, your hair color didn't matter.
UTAGE: It was your hard work
that moved everyone's hearts.
TAMON: But...
TAMON: Honestly, my hair is basically the idol.
UTAGE: I think you mean god.
TAMON: Well...
TAMON: Unlike Ouri-kun, I'm not special at all.
TAMON: Not to mention, I'm a failure,
so all I can do is work hard.
TAMON: Just knowing there are people out there
who'll cheer for someone like me
TAMON: fills me with so much joy...
SIGN: Tamon-kun
TAMON: That's why I want to make everyone happy.
TAMON: And I want everyone to smile.
TAMON: I don't want people
to see me being pathetic.
TAMON: I want people to like me.
UTAGE: It's like you're in love.
TAMON: Huh?
UTAGE: Oh, um... that's just
what it looked like to me.
UTAGE: It's just like
the hallucinations I usually see.
UTAGE: Even if you don't have feelings
for one specific person,
UTAGE: I figured this might actually
be like love to you, Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: And if that's the case,
maybe you already know the answer .
TAMON: Love...
UTAGE: Wanting others to be happy
or wanting them to smile...
UTAGE: It's those feelings.
TAMON: It is?
UTAGE: Um... I don't really understand it
that well myself,
UTAGE: but I just hope that's what
love ends up feeling like for you.
UTAGE: And so...
UTAGE: The fact that you work so hard,
Gloomyhara-senpai...
UTAGE: is also love!
UTAGE: Oh, they've started!
UTAGE: Wow...
UTAGE: Wanting others to be happy
or wanting them to smile...
UTAGE: It's those feelings.
TAMON: Kino...
TAMON: No.
TAMON: Thank you, Uta-chan.
UTAGE: Cha—
UTAGE: Not Kinoshita-san
or even Utage, but "chan"?!
UTAGE: He chose something in between?!
TAMON: Oh...
TAMON: Is what I'm feeling right now love, too?
UTAGE: No, absolutely not.
UTAGE: It's the camaraderie from
pretending to be friends,
UTAGE: but not really.
It's just a fleeting illusion.
TAMON: O-Oh, I see. I'm sorry.
UTAGE: That was close.
UTAGE: Tamon-kun's so earnest that he almost
had a world-ending misunderstanding.
TAMON: But now I feel like I'll be
able to win the second round.
UTAGE: That's great. I'll be cheering you on
as your fan and your housekeeper.
TAMON: I'll do my best.
UTAGE: By the way, what will you be
doing for the second round?
TAMON: Um...
MC: Who is the F/ACE of F/ACE?
MC: And now, we begin the second round
of our competition to decide the center!
MC: A complete 180 from our
first round of visual battles,
MC: they'll be doing something
much more physical this time.
MC: Today, they'll literally
be running on water!
MC: And in first place,
we have Tamon Fukuhara!
MC: Congratulations! No one could compete
with your speed and drive!
TAMON: Thank you very much!
TAMON: I ran with my heart filled with
my love to my girlfriends.
UTAGE: Tamon-kun...
What happened to finding love?
MC: Could we get a message for all
the E/YES supporting you out there?
TAMON: Did you guys see that?
TAMON: You'd better be ready to accept my love.
RIKO: It sure must be rough being an idol.
YUINA: Yet we're part of the problem for
sitting here enjoying their suffering.
UTAGE: Yup, yup.
Credits: \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTranslation:
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSubtitle Timing:
\h\h\hEditing and Typesetting:
Credits: Michelle Tymon
\h\hMariana Martinez
Ashley Barboza
Credits: \h\h\h\h\hQuality Control:
Translation Check:
Credits: Alicia Ashby\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Sriram Gurunathan
LYRICS: Uh huh...
LYRICS: Na na na...
LYRICS: I wonder what the world
would look like without you
LYRICS: When I look back,
you've always been by my side
LYRICS: Teaching me what "warmth"
and "happiness" feel like
LYRICS: A speedboat sails across the endless skies
LYRICS: An unwavering course,
a straight shot down the middle
LYRICS: An unbreakable red balloon
found nowhere else
LYRICS: Is this "fate"? Or just a "coincidence"?
LYRICS: Like a wilted flower coming back to life
LYRICS: A light that shines
LYRICS: Through the impossibly dark night
LYRICS: (Light of your soul)
LYRICS: I wanted to grasp it
LYRICS: (I love you so)
LYRICS: So I strived for it
LYRICS: Wanna keep going, wanna keep growing
LYRICS: Bringing our flowers and dreams
into full bloom